A Guide to the Ancel E. Nunn Papers, 1943-2008
Nunn, Ancel E., Papers
- Stored remotely at Library Storage Facility (LSF):
  - Ancel Nunn papers 1943-2008
    - Executed artworks files 1969-2008, undated (Box 2008-252/2)
      - 7501 Odyssey undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7502 Remember Me To One Who Lives There 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7503 The Golden Spike 1975-1979, 1991, 2003, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7504 The Magic Window 1975-1979, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7505 Sunny Side undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7506 Angelina 1975-1976, 1985, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7507 Come Saturday Morning 1983, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7508 The Awakening undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7509 Reverie undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7510 The Patriot undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7511 The Tethered Nomad 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7512 End of the Season undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7513 Good Morning America 1973-1982, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7514 The Door 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7515 The Gilded Mirror 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7516 Bertha undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7517 Tethered Nomad, Lithograph 75 [1975?]-1978 (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7601 Kelly’s Partner 1976 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/4)
      - 7602 Upper Window 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7603 The Two Lives of Geronimo undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7604 White Horse 1976, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7605 The Hiding of Lone Wolf undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7606 The Fallen Vision of Isa-Tai undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7607 Quannah Parker undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7608 Southwest Airlines: Five Years On 1976, 1990-1992, 2007, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7609 The Blue Cup 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7610 Saturday Morning, (1976) 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7611 The Ladder 1976 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7612 The Sound of a Silent Clock undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7613 A Bed of Leaves 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7614 The Teaparty undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7615 The Passing of Innocence 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7616 The Circle 1976 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7701 The Preening undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7702 An American Heritage undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7703 The Tempest undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7704 A Distant Summer undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7705 Portrait of C.M. Copeland Aug. 1977 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7706 Toward Post 1977, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7707 Nomad undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7708 The Tethered Nomad No. 2 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7801 Passing Seasons undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7802 The Change of Season 1978 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7803 Fallen Angel undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7804 Squall Line 1978 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7805 Winters Farmer 1978 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7806 Hired Hand 1978 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7807 Chores 1978 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7808 The Paper Dove 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7809 Dallas Courthouse (Old Road) undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7810 Illusion, 1 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7811 Illusion, 2 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7812 Genesis, 1 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7813 A Silent Echo undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7814 All Things Considered undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7815 The Kings Highway undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7816 Periwinkles undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7817 The Centaur 1986, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7818 The Nautilus undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7819 Mitre Peak 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7820 Reign undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7821 Lincoln County 1983, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7822/8103 The Edge of Eternity 1978-1986, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7823 Winter’s Corn, 78 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7824 Equine Gilded 1978 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7825-a “And Where Goes The Parade” book related 1977-1980, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7901 Menagerie undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7902 The Butterfly undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7903 Peaceful Kingdom 1979 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7904 Angelina County Lumber Co. General Store, ca. early 30’s 1980-1981, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7905 A Distant Toll undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7906 Soft brown Rain 1979 1979, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7907 Memorial Day undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7908 A New Morning 79 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7909 Van-Guard, Serigraph 1979 1979-1991, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 7909 Van-Guard, Serigraph 1979-A 1979-1980, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8001 A Monday Morning undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8002 A Backward Glance 1980 1986, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8003 The Flight of Proteus 1983, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8004 Harmony 1980 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8005 The Silent Running 1980, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8006 Adoration of the Majo 1980, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8007 Treasures 1980 1980 (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8008 Chalk Line 1980 1980, 1998 (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8009 Sabine County Jail 1980 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8101 The New Road 1981 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8102 Regeneration 1981 1981 (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8103 Day Bed 1981 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8104 Monday Morning #2 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8105 A Warm Winter’s Day 81 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8106 Godfrey’s Spring 1981 litho undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8107 Renfro’s Valley Renfro Valley 1981 1981, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8108 The Temptations of Edward’s Son 1981 1986, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8109 Winter’s Hill 1981 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8110 Day Bed lithograph October 1981 1981, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8111 A Postman’s Holyday ’81 undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8112 Come Saturday Morning, litho Dec. 1981 1982-1983, undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8113 The Pursuer undated (Box 2008-252/5)
      - 8114 The Temptations of Edward’s Son #2 1986, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8201 The Fallen Vision of Isa Tai lithograph 1982 1982-1986, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8202 Rapunzel w/c 82’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8203 The Painted Sky, w/c 82’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8204 A Collection of Visitant’s w/c 82’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8205 The Day Ben Saw the Moon, When It Lost Its Memory w/c 82’ 1981-1982, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8206 Soft Summer Breeze 82’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8207 A Day In June 82’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8208 Chimney Swift 82’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8209 Flightless Spirit undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8301 Distant Summers 1983 1983, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8302 Egg In Space a/p 1983 1983, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8303 The Edge of Eden 83 1984, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8304 An American Crisis 1937 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8305 Genesis #1, reconstructed undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8306 Directions Untethered 83’ 1989, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8401 Uncloistered 1984 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8402 The Spirit of Paul Revere 1984, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8403 Toward The Morningside 84 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8404 Escape ’84 1986, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8405 Sundown 84’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8406 The Madonna 84’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8407 The Edge of Time 84’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8408 Remnants From The Milky Way undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8409 The Sand Dollar 84’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8410 Passing Seasons 84’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8411 Theseus and the Minotaur undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8412 Nude Study 84’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8413 December’s Sun 84’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8501 Toward New Jerusalem 85 1985-1993, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8502 The Return 85’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8503 The Judgement of Juan Seguin 85’ 1985, 1998, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8504 The Windmill Tank 1985 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8505 Remnants From The Milky Way #2 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8506 Labyrinth 85 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8507 Directions Untethered #2 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8601 The Volunteer 1986, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8602 One Century and Fifty litho 1986 1986-1988, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8603 Fall 1985; W/C study undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8604 The Chair 1986 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8605 Imbibo 1986 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8606 Time, Repeating Itself 1986 undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8607 Thursday Afternoon – Aug. 86’ Time repeating itself serie undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8608 Thursday Afternoon #2 Sept. 86’ Time repeating itself serie 1986, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8609 The Death of Persiphone 83-86 1983-1986 (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8610 I Heard a Voice Calling My Name 86’ 1986 (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8611 The Quarry 86’ 1993 (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8612 Sons of Herman nov. 86’ 1999, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8701 Reality and the Scheme of Things 87’ undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8702 Nude Studies – 1, 2, 3 1986, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8703 Object Found litho 1987-1988, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8704 The Talisman Stage 12 1987 (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8705 The Elysian Fields 87’ III 1987-1996, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8706 Thursday Afternoon #2 litho edition ’87 1987, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8707 Nude – study #4 watercolor undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8801 Pars Pro Toto litho 1988 A part for the whole 1988, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8802 Remnants of Change 1988-2008, undated (Box 2008-252/6)
      - 8901 Possessions, I 1989 undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 8902 The Possessor 1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 8903 Possessions #3 oct. 89’ undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9001 Thoughts of Spring 1990 (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9001 Thoughts of Spring 1990 (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9002 A Moment in Time Jan. 90’ undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9003 “Aggregatio Mentium” Feb. 90’ (lat. “A Meeting of Minds”) 1990, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9004 Possessions –IV 1995, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9005 Possessions #5 – Nude Study pencil undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9006 Nude studies, ab undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9007 Possessions #6 undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9008 Mime at rest, Carsons Barnes Circus Series undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9009 The Fallen Star 1990-1991, 2004, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9010 All About Teachers 1990-1991, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9011 Anticipation undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9012 Passerby’s 1990 1991, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9013 Seago, Texas 1990 (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9101 “The Widow” 91 undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9102 “Approaching Storm” pencil 91’ undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9103 “Procrastination” 91 undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9104 “All About Justice” 91’ undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9105 “A Song of Solitude” 91 undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9106 “In Search of Reality” series of six lithographs Edition – 12 [1991?]-1996 (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9201 “Portrait of Roy Emerson” 1991-2001, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9202 “Errands” undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9203 “Trunk I and Trunk II” cont. w. Litho suites “In Search of R.” 1992, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9204 “Coming Are The Doves To Sing For Me” 92 1992-1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9205 Pencil – Old YMCA Bldg. c. 1908 from photo (donation) 92’ 1992, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9206 “The Time Machine of Edwards Son” 1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9207 “The Temptation of Edwards Son, III”1993 undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9208 “Coming Are The Doves” (Study) undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9209 “A Fanfare To The Common Man” 1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9210 “The Rabbit Run” 1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9211 “Time Repeating Itself, II” 1993-1995, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9212 “The Possessor, II” 1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9213 “Confessions” 1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9214 “The Cupboard of Dionysus” 1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9301 “A Reunion” undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9302 “Geometrical and Natural Forms” 1994, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9303 Compatible Objects / 9303-A The Funeral Of – What’s His Name? 1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9304 “The Utopian” 93’ 1998, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9305 “Recurring Moments” 1993 (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9306 “Passerby” 1993-1995, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9307 “The Dwelling of Naiads” 93’ 1993 (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9308 “The Gate and Beyond” undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9309 The Sensor 1993, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 940A Pencil – Pen Ink works undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9401 Persuasion 1994 (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9402 Ascension 1994 (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9403 “The Gift” (Empirical Knowledge) 1994, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9404 “Seline” 1994, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9405 “Points of View” 1994, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9406 A Midwestern Spring undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9407 Apprehension 1994, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9408 “Introspect” 94 1994, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 950A Pencil Pen Ink Works undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9501 “Golden Blind” (Caddo Lake) 1995, undated (Box 2008-252/7)
      - 9502 “Passerby, II” undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9504 20 Pencil Studies Drawings 1995-1999, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9505 “Dr. Jay” Portrait of Dr. Jay Herrington undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9601 “I Am A Purse” 1996-1999, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9602 “Compromise Compromised” litho editions 1-30 1996-1999, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9603 “The Flyway” 1996, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9604 “Recorder of Time” 1996-1998, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9605 “Expectations” undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9606 “Genesis I Reconstructed” (I) undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9607 “Genesis I Reconstructed” (II) 1999-2000, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9608 “The Theft” 1997, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 96 “Ancel Nunn” Limited Edition Books 1-100 1996-1997, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9701 “Pandora’s Box – Reconstructed” undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9702 “Defiance” 1997 1997-2001 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9801 “An Isolated Moment” 1998-2000 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9802 “Out of the Caddo” 1997-2007, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9803 “Voices in the Wind, II” 1998 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9804 “Time Repeating Itself, III” 1998, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9805 “Deceptive Truth” acrylic on paper 1997-1999 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9901 The Guardian undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9902 “A Silent Running” 1999 1999 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9903 “On the Other Side of the Sun” 1999-2008, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - 9904 Voices in the Wind II 1999, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - ?? Paintings – Whereabouts, unknown, perhaps Gallery sales undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Assorted 1993, 2006, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Record book undated (Box 2008-252/8)
    - Patron Files 1968-2008 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Abell, Dr. Joseph Jr. [1976?] (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Alldredge, Max 1975-1993 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - American References ? 89-91 Les Krantz 1988-1992 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Anderson, Alford E. Jr. 1978-1986, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Anderson, Betty F. 1968-1982 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Ashcraft, Claud 1991-1997 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Ashley, Robert 1973-[1976?] (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Atlantic Richfield Company 1978-1982 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Attal, George M. 1980-2003 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Austin, Jeff 1978, 1992 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Bailey Funeral Home 1978, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Baldwin, Scott Baldwin, F. Scott Jr. 1972, 1984-1999 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Barendure, Miss Leta M. undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Barron, Jim + Julie undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Beadle, Don 1968-[1976?] (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Beadle, Holly 1975-1980 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Belanger, Jim [1976?] (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Bochow, Carl E. Mr. Mrs. 1981-1983, 1999, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Bonner, Neal atty. 1977-2002 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Bonniwell, Mrs. Charles [1976?] (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Boone, James C. Jr. 1983, 1997-2003, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Branda, Eldon 1976-1981, 1992-1999, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Brons, Tom 1976 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Brookshire, Bruce 1973-2006, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Brower, Gary 1972-1976 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Burch, Dr. Larry Mrs. (Mimi) 1986-1999, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Burchette, Ray Jr. 1986-1999, undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Burrell, Jack L. undated (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Byram, Robert 1976 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Caldwell, Clifton 1972-1976, 1989 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Caldwell, Louise 1972-1978, 1996, 2001 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Calhoun, Mike 1975-2004 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Cameron, Dr. Harold 1976 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Campbell, Ben D. 1976-2004 (Box 2008-252/8)
      - Carroll, Don Dr. undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Carson, Carol J. 1974-1977 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Carter, Wendell C. Mr. Mrs.. 1980-1991 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Champion, John G. 1982-2004 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Chantillis, Peter S. 1977-1978 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Charnes, Abe 1976 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Chenault, Mike Mr. Mrs. 1983-1998 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Clark, James E. 1975-1986, undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Clippings – other Artist’s writer, miscl. – funnies undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Cooksey, Mr. James G. 1976 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Copeland, John 1976-2000 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Cossner, John (Bank of East Texas) 1986 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Cox, Dr. Robert G. 1972-2000 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Craig, George 1993-1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Crain, Dr. Burton 1976-1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Crocker, William M. 1976-2003 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Crook, Jim 1978 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Crossno, Ronald Dr. Mrs. Carla 1992-1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Crump, Roy A +/ Norelius, Allen J. 1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Cumby, John H. (Mr. and Mrs.) 1978-2001 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Currie, Capt. Don 1972-1998 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Darryl, Dennis 1975-2004 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Davenport, G.G. 1968-1998 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Delaney, Mr. Mrs. Paul Kansas Collectibles 1979-1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Dempsey, Vickie + Henry 1985-2007 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Dorfman, Myron (Ph. D.) 1975-1982 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Duncan, Frank Dr. Melinda 1994-2004 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Duncan, Hamilton 1971-1976, undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Duncan, R.H. Mr. Mrs. 1981, undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Dunkin, Dial 1973-1976 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Durrett, Larry K. 1989, undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Edwards, Bill 1976-1985 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Eisenhower, Dwight + Pat (Tom) undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Elder, Frank III undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Elliott, James T. Jr. 1976-1978 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Elliott, James T. III 1973-1993 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - English (Bruyere), Jane 1978-1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Ethridge, John M. 1976 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Evans, Phillip R. Mr. Mrs. 1988-2007 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Faulconer, Mr. Mrs. Vernon 1980-1996 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Filer, Robert Mrs. Former Kenneth Iceman 1971-1990 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Fitzgerald, James Mr. Mrs. 1986-1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Fleet, Robert 1973-1976 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Fooshee, Mrs. J.B. 1972 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Forbes, D.W. 1976 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Foster, Mrs. Joe Davis 1976-1994 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Gaines, Henry Mr. Mrs. 1979-1997 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Garrett, Jaspar 1976-2000 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - George, Jesse, Jr. Mr. Mrs. 1992-2000 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Giddens, Lesley undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Glaze, Robert 1976-1994 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Gragg, Beth (Mrs. Jack) 1979-1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Graubard, Belle 1976 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Green, Patrick Mr. Mrs. Atty. 1981-1997 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Gregg, Jon Mr. Mrs. 1977-2003 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Grigsby, Cuin 1972-1997 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Gross, William D. 1975-2003 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Guerin, Jo and Dean 1996, undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Guinn, J. Donald 1975-1981 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Hale, Toby 1976-1998 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Hammill, Dr. Donald D. Ed. D. 1990-2004 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Haralson, Hal 1971-1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Harkins, Mrs. H.B. now A.C. Black 1973-1993 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Harrison, Francesca Bruce 1990-1991 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Havenrah, Harry A. Estate 1975 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Hearon, Robert 1976 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Henderson, George 1975-1998 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Herkimer, Sharon, Ann 1994, undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Herrington, Paul undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Hicks, R.M. 1972-1983, undated (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Hinson, Howard 1983-1999 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Howard, Mr. Mrs. Anthony E. 1978-1996 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Howard, Mrs. Virginia 1976 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Howell, Mr. Mrs. Jim 1985-2002 (Box 2008-252/9)
      - Hutchinson, Elizabeth 1975-2003 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Jenkins, John 1976-1989 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Jenkins, O.M. 1995-1999 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Jentz, Gaylord 1976-1980 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Johnson, K.G. undated (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Johnson, Willard 1976 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Johnson, Willard Jr. 1976 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Jones, A.V. Jr. 1972-1989 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Jones, Jon Rex. 1972-1976 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Jones, Richard 1986-1999 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Jowell, Mrs. Gwen undated (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Kane, Tom 1976-2000 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Keenan, Jim. Mr. Mrs. 1981, undated (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Kelso, Robert 1987, undated (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Kimberlin, Sam O. 1968-1978 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Koen, William Jr. 1976-1997 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Kush, Mrs. J.A. 1971-2000 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Kuykendall, Mrs. Charles 1972-1976, undated (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Kuykendall, Gill 1976-2002 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Law, Harold 1972-1977 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Leon, Henry 1972-2002 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Lockridge, Mr. Mrs. Jack 1980-2006 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Long, Mrs. James W. 1976 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Mack, Dr. Leo W. Jr. 1989-2007 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Mackenzie, Don Gallery 1990, undated (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Maffitt, Ted 1976 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Magruder, Leonard 1968-2004 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Mallard, Jon L. III 1972-1976 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Mallette, Weldon 1973-1987 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Marley Co. f. Wylain 1977-1982 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Maurer, Robert 1972-1990 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Mayo, Larry 1981-1999 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - McAllen, Robert 1970-1989, undated (Box 2008-252/10)
      - McClain, Mrs. R.K. now Emily McClain Stroble 1973-1991 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - McDonald, Jim Mr. Mrs. 1981-1998 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - McKnight, Payton 1986 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - McNutt, William Lee, Jr. 1976-1996 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Menn, Arnold 1976-1996 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Mezayek, M.S. Mr. Mrs. 1985-1999 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Miller, Robert 1976-2000 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Miller, Townsend 1976-1987 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Moore, Thomas 1981-1998 (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Muench, Joann Tunnell 1983-2003, undated (Box 2008-252/10)
      - Muntz, Mrs. Robert 1976-2004 (Box 2008-252/10)